oliverbonas.com 2013-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Oliver Bonas

### Data Protection

Oliver Bonas LTD is a registered data user under the Data Protection Act.

We will never pass on your details on to a third party for marketing purposes. We may contact you with promotions we think might interest you, as part of our market research, either by mail, telephone or email.

As with all retail websites, we collect personal information when opening your account and processing your orders. We will automatically collect information such as your browser IP address to make shopping with us easier, for example, remembering your log-in details.

The information we collect is:

  * Your name, so we know who you are
  * Email address, so we can email you order confirmations, delivery delays, offers etc.
  * Delivery address, an obvious one
  * Date of Birth - so we can send you a pressie!
  * Telephone number, we'll only call if we have a delivery problem.
  * Credit card details, we only ask for these when you place an order.

If you have questions about your personal data or our privacy policy, please contact us at orders@oliverbonas.com.

We use the latest secure server technology to ensure this information is protected to the highest standards. We use encryption to safeguard your credit card information and only accept orders from web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology - this means you cannot inadvertently place an order through an unsecured connection. Most web browsers above version three support this security. This encryption makes it virtually impossible for unauthorised parties to read any information that you send us. The encryption technique we use is the highest standard available for e-commerce.

### Privacy Policy

Any information we collect about customers' browsing and buying habits is used to improve the Oliver Bonas website and the products and services offered to our customers. It also assists us with the detection and prevention of fraud.

We use this information to make your shopping experience as easy and enjoyable as possible. We need it to process your order, inform you of any delays or problems and occasionally to send you special offers and promotions.

We control information we have collected about you that is relevant to your account. This includes:

  * Online customers will require a log-in and password to access their account.
  * Our courier service will have selected access to your details for delivery purposes only.

All Oliver Bonas customers have the option to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us and/or selected third parties.

If you do not wish to continue to receive marketing from us you should opt-out by visiting 'Your Details' in 'Your Account' on the Oliver Bonas website, or click on the "unsubscribe" link in any email communications which might we send you.

Third party sites: Our site may contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

### Cookies

We will use cookies (electronic tags) to monitor your browsing and buying habits on our site, for example, which pages are visited, and whether they are purchased from. If you have registered with us then your computer will store an identifying cookie which will save you time each time you re-visit Oliver Bonas, by remembering your email address for you. You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies being stored on your computer without your explicit consent.

If you have questions about your personal data or our privacy policy, you can write to us at:

Oliver Bonas Website  
Unit F Davis Road Industrial Estate  
Davis Road Chessington  
KT9 1TQ

"It is not the critic who counts, not the man who points out how the strong man stumbled, or where the doer of deeds could have done better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood….. "  ~ Theodore Roosevelt
